export const questions=[
    {
        prompt:'Who is the king of cricket?',
        optionA:'sachin',
        optionB:'Kohli',
        optionC:'sehwag',
        optionD:'Rohit',
        answer:'B'
    },
    {
        prompt:'Which is the perfect square?',
        optionA:'25',
        optionB:'15',
        optionC:'27',
        optionD:'30',
        answer:'A'
    },
    {
        prompt:' Most international runs in   womens?',
        optionA:'Devine',
        optionB:'kaur',
        optionC:'Mandhana',
        optionD:'Mithali',
        answer:'D'
    },
    {
        prompt:'Who hits first IPL century?',
        optionA:'Brendon McCullum',
        optionB:' virat Kohli',
        optionC:'Manish Pandey',
        optionD:'sachin',
        answer:'A'
    },
    {
        prompt:'Which country was invented cricket?',
        optionA:'Aus',
        optionB:'NZ',
        optionC:'Ind',
        optionD:'Eng',
        answer:'D'
    },
    {
        prompt:'Who is the father of mathematics?',
        optionA:'Ramanujan',
        optionB:'Archimedes',
        optionC:'W.G.Grace',
        optionD:'Mohammad Dhoni',
        answer:'B'
    },
    {
        prompt:'Which country has no mosquitoes?',
        optionA:'Iceland',
        optionB:'singapore',
        optionC:'sweden',
        optionD:'Norway',
        answer:'A'
    },
    {
        prompt:'25% of 200 is?',
        optionA:'100',
        optionB:'75',
        optionC:'25',
        optionD:'50',
        answer:'D'
    },
    {
        prompt:'2,4,16,_?',
        optionA:'144',
        optionB:'246',
        optionC:'256',
        optionD:'198',
        answer:'C'
    },
    {
        prompt:'1,2,3,2,9,4,_?',
        optionA:'27',
        optionB:'32',
        optionC:'21',
        optionD:'18',
        answer:'A'
    },
]